Today we're going to focus on the Caribbean and the various attacks on the
sovereignty of Caribbean nations. We're going to start with Borinquen, Puerto Rico
that remains occupied illegally by the U.S. government and through the U.S.
military for over 127 years as we continue to struggle for our
sovereignty. The U.S. has deployed the initial 4,500 troops and an additional
10,000 troops last week along with F-35s, GBU-32 missiles that are being used in
Gaza to attack the sovereignty of another nation, Venezuela. This is a continuation
of a long history of experimentation using our country as a launch pad for
attacks throughout the region. The U.S. has seven active military bases and it is
using this to launch the attacks. There have been 43 extrajudicial killers
killings, mostly in the Caribbean but also in the Pacific, no justification. One
of the U.S. warships that was docked in Borinquen has made its way to Trinidad and
Tobago. Two Trinbagonians have been part of these extrajudicial killings that we
are demanding justice for. The Prime Minister of Trinidad and Tobago is
complicit and a U.S. puppet allowing the U.S. warships to dock and justifying these
extrajudicial killings. 41 years ago, the U.S. committed the assassination of our
comrade Maurice Bishop and they launched these attacks through Barbados because at
the time the Prime Minister of Trinidad and Tobago believed in the sovereignty of
Grenada. Almost 41 years after his assassination, the U.S. is trying to force a
U.S. military outpost in Grenada at the Maurice Bishop Airport. What disrespect.
They're trying to force this by attacking the fish industry in Grenada and it's
important to note that 90% of fish exports go to the U.S. to stop the import of
fish from Grenada to try to force the nation to allow the U.S. to build this
illegal military installation. The U.S. is using Southcom to attack the
sovereignty of Venezuela to steal its oil and resources under the false
accusation that Maduro is a drug lord. We know that most of the drugs that
entered the U.S. in collaboration with the CIA as has been approved in the past
is coming in through the Pacific Ocean. So this is a lie. The U.S. is using
Borinquen as a launch pad to send troops and warships to Trinidad and Tobago,
Guyana, as well as trying to use Grenada and surround the coast of Venezuela and
attack. On top of all this, the world's largest nuclear-powered aircraft carrier,
the USS Gerald Ford, is on its way to the Caribbean. And what was it before then?
...